<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="food_category">Food</string>
    <string name="education_category">Education</string>
    <string name="attractions_category">Attractions</string>
    <string name="stemple">Someshwar Temple</string>
    <string name="kelgeri">Kelgeri Lake</string>
    <string name="sadankeri">Sadankeri Lake</string>
    <string name="ulavi">Ulavi Temple</string>
    <string name="avalakki">Tuppad Avalakki</string>
    <string name="girmit">Girmit</string>
    <string name="rotti">Rotti</string>
    <string name="pedha">Pedha</string>
    <string name="sdme">SDM College of Engineering and Technology</string>
    <string name="sdmm">SDM College of Medical Sciences and Hospital</string>
    <string name="agri">University of Agricultural Sciences</string>
    <string name="kar">Karnatak University</string>
    <string name="about_sadankeri">Sadhankeri,located on the North East outskirts of Dharwad is known for its cultural roots. Dr. Da. Ra. Bendre, the Jnanpeeth Award winning Kannada literature lived in Sadhankeri, where he composed most of his poetry. Sadhankeri was also home to Alur Venkatarao, who was instrumental in integration of Karnataka as a single linguistic state. Shambha Joshi (Jadabharata), Varadaraj Huilgol, Neglur Ranganath etc. all were other stalwarts of Kannada literature who lived here. Today, this lush green locality, surrounding the Sadhankeri Lake is a bustling suburb of Hubli-Dharwad. Plans are afoot to develop the lake as an important tourist spot as Baaro Sadhanakerige Project.</string>
    <string name="about_kelgeri">Kelgeri lake, known for its natural beauty and serene atmosphere, and is the legacy of Sir M. Visvesaraya. Nestled amidst idyllic surroundings, this 230-acre water body has played a key role in the development of Dharwad and has become an integral part of its culture and has been a source of inspiration for poets and writers of the land.</string>
    <string name="about_ulavi">Ulavi Basaveshwara Gudi is situated on a hillock. This shrine\'s history goes back to 12th century i.e. Basavaeshwara\'s time. Back then the  was known as Basappana Gudda, it is said that a shrine existed here since then. The hill gained importance when Basaveshwara\'s sister Nagalambike and her son Chennabasaveshwara camp here during their journey from Kalyana (in Bidar district) to Ulavi (in Uttara Kannada jungles).</string>
    <string name="about_stemple">Someshwara temple is one of the oldest and most revered places of this city. This temple was built during the Chalukya dynasty and from then it evolved as a great religious place. The major features of this place are the surroundings and the of course the idols of Chatrubhuja and Mahishasur Mardini which are very old and were established here by the Chalukya ruler. Lots of people visit this temple during the Ganesha Chaturthi festival which is celebrated here. This temple is surrounded by lush green grasslands and beautiful plants which add an aura to the place.</string>
    <string name="about_agri">University of Agricultural Sciences, Dharwad is a state agriculture university established by the Government of Karnataka which imparts education, research and extension activities in the fields of agriculture, forestry, food science, agri marketing and home science. The university was started on 1 October 1986</string>
    <string name="about_sdme">Shri Dharmasthala Manjunatheshwara College of Engineering and Technology, Dharwad was established in the year 1979 under the flagship of SDME Society and has grown into one of the nationally acclaimed premier engineering institutions in the country. The President of SDME Society Padmabhushana Dr. Veerendra Heggade, Dharmadhikari of Sri Kshetra Dharmasthala is the guiding spirit and driving force for all the progress and achievements of all the institutions established under SDME Society. SDME Society runs more than 30 institutions imparting quality education in all over the state including Medical and Dental colleges.</string>
    <string name="about_sdmm">“Royal treatment for common man” has been the mission statement of SDM Hospital. Every person who has taken treatment in this Hospital would certainly feel this.  The clean environment and humble services of staff have been making plenty of people recover their health every day. Hospital is also fostering quality research in medical field.  Regular workshops and conferences are being conducted to enhance the knowledge of doctors working within the Hospital and also those within twin cities. For the community, Hospital conducts regular free health camps, family planning camps, cataract camps, spirometry camps etc.  Within very short span since its inception, under the able leadership of Dr. Niranjan Kumar, Medical Director, this Hospital has made a prominent name in the medical map of India. </string>
    <string name="about_uni">Karnatak University, Dharwad is a UGC (University Grants Commission) declared deemed university in Dharwad, Karnataka. Karnatak University, Dharwad offers higher education through its variety of courses which includes professional degree courses, liberal arts courses, nursing, and distance education courses</string>
    <string name="about_girmit">Girmit is a very popular street food from north Karnataka. This  snack recipe is extremely popular in Hubli-dharwad region of Karnataka.Its usually eaten with Menasinakayi bajji.</string>
    <string name="about_pedha">Dharwad’s other major contribution is the Dharwad Pedha, a mildly sweet, caramelised, version with its trademark coffee brown hue that can trace its roots back to Unnao in Uttar Pradesh.</string>
    <string name="about_rotti">Jolada Rotti is very popular in North Karnataka which is a not just delicious to taste but also good source of nutrients. To make this roties, hands are used instead of rolling pin and are flattened to thin circles using palm. Making Jowar roti is not a child’s play. Experience, skill and patience is required to flatten the dough without breaking the roties and to get puffed roties. Its got the rustic look and unforgettable flavor .</string>
    <string name="about_avalakki">This is very unique dish which is only available at L.E.A Canteen. This is made of mixture of Flattened rice ,ghee,chopped onions ,coconut water etc. This is really a tasty evening snack with some sweetness and little bit of spice. Mind you, one plate is never sufficient. This is MUST try dish at Dharwad.</string>
</resources>
